♪ it seems today that all you see ♪
♪ is violence in movies and sex on tv ♪
♪ but where are those good ol
d-fashioned values ♪
♪ on which we used to rely? ♪
♪ lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ all the things that make us ♪
♪ laugh and cry ♪
♪ he's... A... Fam... Ily... Guy! ♪
Good evening. I'm diane simmons.
In traffic news, heavy gridlock
on the 195 interchange.
We now go live to drunk billy
in the channel 5 newscopter.
This just in.
Channel 5 newscopter pilot
drunk billy passed away today.
In anticipation of this event,
We put together a clip package
Featuring some of billy's
work for channel 5 news.
"I'm still hungry,
" said the very hungry caterpillar.
"but you've already..."
Drunk billy will be missed.
But what you shouldn't
miss is the quahog rodeo,
Coming to the civic center this Friday.
Tickets are on sale now.
And for those of you who
are handy with a horse,
Entry spots are still open.
Oh, god, this seems like
the kind of thing peter...
Too late, brian.
Peter, you're gonna enter the rodeo?
That's stupid.
You don't know anything about horses,
And you're in terrible shape.
You know, that's the difference
between you and me, lois.
When life comes knocking at the door,
You go and hide in the kitchen.
I fling the door wide open and I say,
"peter griffin here. What do you got?"
And if that don't convince you,
look at this.
In this week's tv guide, it says,
"peter gets more than he bargained for
When he joins the rodeo."
Well, it's in the guide.
Hey, can we make that a thing?
Can we start calling tv guide, "the
guide"?
You know what? I'm not even asking anymore.
That's what we're doing.
Who says I couldn't be a rodeo star?
I got more cowboy blood
in me than billy the kid.
♪ well, he robbed his way
from utah to oklahoma ♪
♪ and the law just could not
seem to track him down ♪
♪ and it served his legend well ♪
♪ for the folks, they loved to tell ♪
♪ about when billy the kid came to town. ♪
♪ ♪
Hyah!
Dad, what are you doing?!
All right, meg, this is only gonna hurt
For about three weeks.
What the hell?
That there's my steer, griffin.
All right, lois. Go ahead. Say it.
Chris, it's time for supper.
Ho der, ho der, ho der!
Ho der, ho der, ho der, ho der!
Ho der, ho der, ho der! Ho der, ho der!
Ho der, ho der, ho der.
ho der, ho der, ho der.
Ho der.
All right. I am ready for the rodeo.
Mom, when's it dad's turn?
I don't know, chris.
But I think we should
all pray for your father
That he comes out of this uninjured.
Those horses stink.
And it's too hot in here.
I fell asleep in the car, so now I'm cranky.
This is a disgusting display.
Boy, you can say that again.
Nothing like a bunch of adult
men teasing animals for fun.
It's amazing that this is still legal.
The only reason I'm here
Is 'cause my idiot friend is in the rodeo.
I only came 'cause I'm
writing a magazine article.
One of the competitors
Is a 13-year-old female riding prodigy.
Apparently she got on the bull to miscarry,
And found out she had a talent for it.
Announcer : Ladies and gentlemen,
give an indifferent east coast welcome
To the newest bullrider, peter the kid!
You know what I am back at the ranch?
I'm a breeding bull.
W-what-what's that?
You gonna find out.
Where you goin', fatty?
We gonna have a party.
No! No!
So, what magazine do you write for?
I'm the editor for teen people.
Editor?
Well, gosh, you know,
I'm something of a writer myself.
I-I wrote for the new yorker
for a little while.
Wow, that's impressive.
Are you looking for work?
Oh, no. No, no, no.
I-I never have to look too far for that.
I... W-w-what are you...
What do you... What-what do you got?
Well, we're looking for
someone to write a piece
On the everyday activities
Of the average american teenage girl.
Oh, I love teenage girls.
It's all ahead of them, you know?
They haven't turned into bitches yet.
Oh, it's true.
What happened to all of us?
I got a house on the cape.
Maybe you come visit.
Maybe.
Maybe you call a few days in advance
To give me time to get the house clean.
Okay.
Maybe you bring a blazer,
So we can go to a wider
range of restaurants.
I'll-I'll bring a blazer.
You see this, rupert?
Most children build a sand castle.
But I'm building a sand retreat
for singles in their 30s.
: Hi, I'm jeremy.
I work in corporate finance.
: Hi, I'm a french canadian girl
Down here on my vacation.
It's a big deal for me to
be down here on my own.
I like the swimming pool with a bar in it
'cause you can sit on a barstool
and you're in the water.
: I like how all the food
and drink is included
In the price of the ticket.
: Yeah, that way you don't have
To bring your cash down from the room.
: Okay, I was just looking
for a friend of mine,
So maybe I'll see you later.
: Good for you, janine.
You promised yourself you'd
talk to somebody and you did it.
: Brian, what are you doing up there?
Shh. I'm writing an article
On teenage girls for a magazine.
I'm studying meg to see
what goes on during her day.
Well, be careful you don't
fall off that ladder.
Not all dogs go to heaven.
So, says here you were involved
In the plotting of September 11?
Well, that's what they get
for supporting israel.
Hyuck, yuck, yuck. Gawsh.
Okay, into the eternal pit of fire you go.
Wa-hoo-hoo-hoo-ee!
You know, brian, just because
you're writing a profile
On teenage girls, it doesn't mean you have
To be a creepy stalker and
follow meg around all day.
It's called research, stewie.
I'm just being thorough.
Where the hell is she going?
There's nothing out in this part of town.
What is that, brian?
What is an adult correctional institute?
It's a prison, stewie.
Ah.
One would think they could just say that.
Hi, meg.
Hi, luke.
Oh, my god.
Meg's dating a convict!
Oh looks like consuela's son is in prison.
I see you soon, rodrigo.
Si, mama.
It's really good to see you, meg.
It's been a while.
I know. I'm sorry, luke.
It's just so hard to get over here
Without anybody finding out.
Have you gotten all the letters
and hair that I've sent?
It's the only thing
That's getting me by, meg. Thank you.
How'd your parole hearing go?
Not good.
Looks like I'm gonna be in
here another three years.
Oh, luke.
Oh, I don't expect you to wait for me, meg.
No, I will, luke.
If it takes ten years or 20 years,
I will be here when you get out.
Oh, my god!
Meg's involved with a convict!
Wow, meg's like one of those crazy chicks
Who hooks up with an even crazier guy.
Brian, you bastard!
How could you do this to me?!
I'm sorry, meg. I had to tell them!
Don't give him crap for this, meg.
He did exactly the right
thing by coming to us.
Don't you know what kind of fire
You're playing with, dating a prisoner?
Hold on, lois. This is
some serious parenting.
I'm gonna go put on my cosby sweater.
Mom, you don't understand!
Luke and I really connect, very deeply!
He's all alone in there,
and I'm all alone out here.
In a way, we're both in prison.
Well, meg, there's a big difference there.
He's in prison for a reason.
He broke the law!
He robbed a convenience store
To pay for medication for his mom.
Oh, I'm sure he gave you a
very convincing sob story.
It's not a sob story! It's true!
Frankly, I don't care, meg.
I do not want you seeing him again!
I can't find the sweater.
How the hell did you even meet him?!
We had a pen pal project at school,
And when it was over,
Luke and I just kind of
kept writing to each other.
Well, it stops now!
But, mom, I love him!
It stops now, meg!
Your mother's right, meg.
You got to be careful
Who you get involved with romantically.
Hello?
I'm in the mood for some coitus.
Get over here.
I can't. I'm with my family.
Pick up wine on the way.
Well, angela, if I'm
really the only guy at work
Who can solve it, I'll be right there.
Luke!
What are you doing here?!
I escaped, meg.
I escaped 'cause I just couldn't bear
Another second away from you.
My god, how did you get out?
I filed down a toothbrush to a fine point
And stabbed the guard with the most kids.
What?! I'm just kidding.
Oh. I'm still getting used
to your sense of humor.
Actually, there was a
riot in the prison yard,
And I slipped over the fence.
Well, well, quick, get in
here before somebody sees you!
Oh, meg, I've wanted to do that for so long.
And it's nice to be in front
of someone for a change.
Now I know that was a joke!
whatever.
Hey, meg?
Can I talk to you for a second?
Uh, yeah, come on in.
Listen, uh, I feel like
I should explain myself
A little bit here.
I'm sorry I had to tell
lois what was going on.
You just, you gotta realize
I was only thinking about your safety and...
Luke, you might as well come out now.
Luke! What the...
? They let you out of jail?!
Not exactly.
He broke out to see me, brian.
We're in love.
Meg, are you crazy?!
You can't harbor a fugitive.
That's a felony.
Only if someone finds out.
Are you gonna do it?
Are you gonna tell on me again?
Well, I, I...
Brian, will you call me
on my mickey mouse phone?
Wait a second.
Why is that guy wearing a prison jumpsuit?
Think, peter, think.
Wait. Hang on.
Sunday, Sunday... Here it is.
"peter gets more than he bargains for
When he joins the rodeo." boy, did I.
"and meg dates a prison escapee"!
Oh, no! Luke, run!
Joe, it's peter! Two things:
First of all, when I was over
at your house the other day,
I forgot to tell you how
much I like the rearrangement
You and bonnie did with
your living room furniture.
Second of all, come outside!
There's an escaped convict
running across the street!
No, luke, don't run downhill!
You're going to jail, punk!
No, mr. Swanson, you can't take him!
Yes, I can, meg.
He's going back to jail.
Well, if you're taking him to jail,
You have to take me, too!
I know. That's the plan.
You're under arrest for
harboring an escaped convict.
Oh, well, that's only
fair because after all,
I did hide him from the...
What?!
Uh, hi.
Did you also get caught
trying to vote in ohio?
Well, this is it.
Meg gets out of jail today.
Already? It seems like just
yesterday we rented her room
To that fly that wants to leave,
but can't figure it out.
Okay, now where now?
Right there.
I'm having some trouble here.
It's right there!
It's right in front of you!
Okay, I can hear you.
Volume's not a problem.
I'm just not quite seeing
what you're referring to.
Okay, then fly, fly out the window.
Up here maybe? No, to your left!
No, that's not it. That's just more wall.
How many eyes do you have, huh?!
Just two, same number as you,
but I can't, I'm not...
Just go! Oh, my god!
Whatever it is you're driving at,
I'm just apparently not getting it...
You're right there!
...So I'm just gonna go back upstairs.
I think we should all go
together to pick meg up.
She's probably a little fragile
after being in there so long,
And I'm sure she'll be
heartened to see our faces.
I'm home. You're all my bitches now.
Okay.
Meg! You look so different.
How was prison?
First question:
Who's the biggest,
toughest guy in this house?
Well, I don't like to toot my own horn,
But I believe I hold the distinction...
My house now, bitch!
Now who's the funniest?
I know my way around a joke.
For god's sake, dad,
Have some humility! It'll save your life!
There better be beer in the fridge.
Boy, I liked her better when
she was more predictable...
Like the stock photos
on a corporate website.
I'm a woman in a lab coat wearing goggles,
Staring intently at a beaker
that I'm holding near my face.
I'm a latino in a hardhat,
But I'm also wearing a tie
so you know I'm a supervisor.
We're college students
listening to our professor,
But the class is taking
place outside?!
Hey.
Meg! What the hell are you doing in here?!
Shower time. Yeah, for me.
Not-not for... What are you
doing with that loofah?
Don't worry about it.
You told me not to worry about it!
I shoulda been worried the whole time!
Meg, honey? I did all your laundry.
Oh, my god, what is that smell?
It's my poop bucket.
What the hell?!
I'm used to going to the
bathroom in my room.
That's disgusting!
No, you use the toilet
here like everyone else!
No. Ugh!
God, it smells horrible!
Well, can you at least empty
it each time you use it?
I like to fill it up.
I'm not making a million trips.
Oh, my god, are you using
my shirts as toilet paper?
Yeah. And I think
I might need some right now.
Get out now or stay and get weird.
Your call, warden.
Hey, who's the new dude?
Oh, my god, that's meg griffin!
She just got out of prison!
Hey, meg, what'd they put you in jail for,
Being ugly?
Hey, meg, what happened?
Did you get out early for fat behavior?
Nice tattoo.
Did you get your butt hair braided, too,
While you were in there?
What'd you do, carve a gun out of soap
And then not wash with it? Ha-ha! P.U.
Hey, meg, are you gonna take those soda cans
To the shawskank redemption center?
Peter, meg's been suspended from school.
That's okay. Whatever she wants to do.
She cracked three kids' skulls open!
Ever since she's gotten out of prison,
She is completely out of control.
Don't you see?
That's what the penal
system does in this country.
It turns small-time offenders
into hardened criminals.
Look at meg. They took
an innocent little girl
And turned her into a psychotic,
sociopathic freak.
What'd you say, brian?
Oh, I-I was just picking
up on something lois said.
What-what was it? What'd you say, lois?
Something about meg being a freak?
Oh, no, I didn't say anything.
Uh, peter said something about meg,
Which I completely disagree with.
That-that-that wasn't me.
Stewie was really laying
into meg about something.
Yeah, it was stewie.
Definitely stewie.
Oh, so now everyone understands me.
Look, meg, we're just worried about you.
Well, don't. I can take care of myself.
I'll be outta here by the end of the week.
Punch yourself in the face.
Punch yourself in the face!
All right, he doesn't know what he's doing.
You, fatso, punch your baby in the fa...
I did good, meg?
Shut up.
I did good. I did good.
Drive.
Uh, any particular direction?
That way.
You're gonna help me get some money
So I can get out of this town.
Really? Where are you gonna go?
I don't know. Somewhere far away.
Maybe china.
I hear they got nascar there now.
What kind of birdhouse can
you build with popsicles,
Roofies, and a mallet?
It's for a rare african bird called "
nunya business."
Hi, meg. Can I help you?
Hands in the air, goldman!
Oh, my god, what are you doing?!
Gimme your money!
Here, here, just take this jar
For the leukemia kids.
I don't give it to 'em anyhow.
Meg, put down the gun.
Brian, get back in the car!
Look, don't do this. This isn't you, meg.
What happened to the girl we used to know?
The one that luke fell in love with?
The one he's expecting to see
When he steps out of
that prison in 40 years?
I don't care about luke.
I don't need him. I don't need anyone!
Look, if you don't put the gun down,
I'm gonna be forced to call the police.
Good! Call the police!
I want you to!
What do I care if I go back to prison?
Nobody cares about me anyway!
You're wrong, meg.
I wanna show you something.
Teen people?
It's the article I wrote about you.
You wrote an article about me?
They wanted a story
About a typical teenage girl.
Is it "a fistful of backne:
Tale of a teenage loser"?
Yeah, they make the title.
Read paragraph three.
This isn't a library, you know.
"and in the face of every
adolescent challenge,
"she looks at the world through hopeful eyes
"and maintains an uncommon resilience
"that can only be admired.
"in this sense, meg griffin is
not the typical american girl.
She is far sweeter and kinder than that."
Oh, god, that is so nice, brian.
Did you mean all that?
Of course I did.
Oh, my god, I-I can't believe I did this.
I was just so tired of being
everyone's whipping girl
That it felt kind of good
to do some of the whipping.
Give me the gun, meg.
Thanks for reminding me who I really am.
Well, at least I didn't get robbed.
And what can I do for you four
fine black gentlemen today?
I got to say, meg, I like you
so much better like this.
Me, too, meg.
God, it must have been horrible in there.
It wasn't so bad.
I met wesley snipes. Is that right?
Yeah. Oh, and you know what's funny?
He was inmate 57, too.
Huh?
He was inmate 57?
See, he did a movie called
passenger 57.
Ah.
Well, terrific.
Always end on a strong joke.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru